NICHOLAS TOBAT

Front-End Developer

nicktobat.com

WHO, EXACTLY?

I am a fully self-taught developer. I have learned the craft, found my own clients and built my professional reputation from the ground up. I have worked both at home and abroad in Australia. I am methodical yet agile in my work, and accustomed to and comfortable with a fastpaced environment.

Available for both freelance and full-time work.

PROJECTS

FREELANCE GIGS

www.learnsensegrow.com.au

Occupational Therapy practice. Built in WordPress.

www.gordonandcocpas.com

Financial Planning firm.

GoDaddy Website Builder.

www.wharley.com.au

Family bookbinding business. From scratch with Bootstrap.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

My Website (website)

I built a little something

nice for myself: nicktobat.com

Documnt (web app)

Techno and concrete poetry.

Unsuccess (short story)

Life: an existential quandary.

Richmond Marathon (race)

Beat previous time (3:55:56).

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE

Jan 2015 - Present Website Design & Building

BACK OF HOUSE

Aug 2015 - April 2016 Street ADL

PROJECT MGR & SALES REP

Nov - Dec 2014 NCS Moving Services

TECHNICAL RECRUITER

July - Oct 2014 Scaffold Labs

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML(5)
- JavaScript
- CSS(3)
- Angular
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- WordPress Python

EDUCATION

freeCodeCamp

Sep 2015 - Present Full Stack Web Development

Code School & Codeacademy Sep 2014 - Present

University of Virginia

Class of 2014 B.A. Foreign Affairs 3.4 GPA